When will you stop
doing all these, Hadi?
Maya, I promise to marry
you after we done with this.
I love you, Maya.
-I don't believe it.
You've made so many promises.
It'll never be enough for you.
I promise, Maya,
this will be the last time.
I'm tired of waiting for you.
Darling, let's talk later.
Our show is about to start.
Every second,...
...we're looking for a way out...
...from destiny,...
...time...
...and also our own hearts.
I believe...
...in love and life,...
...everyone...
...is looking...
...for a way out.
I believe...
...true love...
...is like magic
Today, I will
show you an illusion...
...about love, courage...
...and freedom.
Tonight,...
...I am not alone.
I am accompanied by my assistant.
A woman who paints
and gives meaning...
...to every one of my magic shows.
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Maya!
Maya will be tied...
...and hung under this car.
There is only one way out.
Maya needs to escape
in less than a minute...
...and go down to
the platform below.
But, ladies and gentlemen,...
...that is not challenging enough.
Maya needs to do all this...
...while all these cables
are on fire...
...and in this car,
there's a bomb...
...that will go off in 60 seconds.
Maya. Are you ready?
Are you ready?
Let's begin!
Fire!
Maya, something's off. Hurry up!
Maya.
Hook, cross, big knee.
One more. Good.
(4 YEARS LATER)
One, two, okay.
One more.
Why are you sighing?
This guy is good.
Queen takes C6
and you will win.
Give up Queen just like that?
Bishop A6, checkmate.
Yes, I won!
You're awesome.
Power.
This is an old car
but with character.
It's unique compared to a new car.
But the car bumper's fallen.
The car bumper's fallen?
This bumper is one of
its personalities, mister.
This car has travelled far.
Lots of experiences, just like you.
Where's the card, mister?
Lucky number 7.
Place it in the middle.
I'll show you
how this car can look better...
...with my magic tricks.
We're here to buy a car.
Not to enjoy a magic show.
Gosh.
-The price can be negotiated!
There's a special
price for senior citizens!
Mister, free mineral water!
(FARIQ
Do not be late)
Mister, we can negotiate the price!
Mister!
Today, we're going to
learn about ethical hacking.
How we can use our coding skills...
...responsibly.
For example, SQL injection.
Teacher This lesson
is for year-one students.
Or is this the only
thing that you know?
Imagine, we can use a proxy tool...
...to intercept HTTP requests.
And with this method,
we can see...
...how code injection can
manipulate a website's database.
(I suggest that you keep quiet
or your parent will know...
...your browsing history
last night. Your choice.)
So, if this website doesn't
have a strong defence system...
...this technique
can bypass log-in.
(FARIQ
Do not be late)
Where are you, Wa? I've
been waiting for eight years.
Wait another eight years.
For you? Anything, Wa.
Wait for my "sorry" cue later.
Then, you can hack.
Sorry, boss.
Done, Fariq. All yours.
What's all this? Who are you?
First day.
Make sure to be alert
There are many people today.
What's up?
Excuse me.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is a very special night.
I want to celebrate the
success of my partner, Sean...
...and my boss, Tommy Tan.
Other than that,....
...I'd like to say welcome back...
...to a special guest of mine...
...who has been missing for years.
A master of his own craft.
The one and only
The Great Hadini.
All this is thanks to
Mr. Tommy Tan.
Without Mr. Tommy,...
...we wouldn't be able to enjoy...
...a magic performance from Hadi.
That must be Dr. Siva.
Check the study room.
The security team knows.
Okay, got it.
Guys, plan B.
Okay, roger. Plan B.
Hassan is so slow.
Hassan, have you checked?
Hassan, where are you?
Whoever is near the study room...
...please check now.
Hassan is useless.
Hassan fainted, boss
He fainted?
Where are you now?
In front of the study room, boss.
I want everyone to go
to Dr. Siva's study room.
Our premise has been compromised!
Everyone go there!
Are you blind?
You didn't hear my instructions?
Boss, the study room
has been compromised.
Sorry, Sean, Tommy.
Something urgent has come up.
It's best if you
both leave right now.
Make sure to settle your problem.
Look for him now.
Hurry up, Fariq. You're so slow.
I know.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Don't run!
-Hey, you!
Give it back to me.
Don't waste my time. Give it back!
Sorry.
Get him!
Dr, where is the toilet?
Khalid! Where's Khalid?
Kill him. Kill him!
Don't move!
Hold on!
Call the police!
-Bring him away.
Check this whole place.
He wouldn't have come alone.
Go and check on Dr. Siva.
You check on the guests. Someone
must have called the police.
Make sure everything is
clear before the police get here.
All right.
Are you blind?
You didn't hear my instructions?
Don't move.
That hurts
Ujang, did you put a bomb?
It's just a little.
You're such a baby.
Such a baby, hello.
Hello.
Good job.
A man has been arrested
for allegedly being involved...
...in organ trafficking syndicate
in the international black market.
Dr. Siva, 48, has been
remanded for seven days.....
No matter how sneaky you are,
you will be caught someday.
Luckily, the police were fast.
This document is the information
mine of Dr. Siva's illegal works.
But there is not a
single transaction...
...that mentions the
name of Tan Sri Hamdan.
Well, he's the leader,
right? Smart.
That's why people
like Dr. Siva exist.
They're only proxies.
What are we doing next?
Are we stalking Hamdan...
...or should we go
straight to Tommy?
Guys!
We have a number-one fan?
Do we even have fans?
You are invited to
a private show of...
...Hadi the magician.
When we were at Dr. Siva's house
I was so excited to find out...
...that Hadi is making a comeback.
Do you know him?
Come on, Wa.
How can you not know
what your boyfriend knows?
Bro, who is your girlfriend?
You don't have to be shy.
Don't make a fuss.
Fariq, I think we need
to make a move.
Four years ago, when
Hadi went off the radar,...
...his assistant, Maya, died.
This is his first appearance.
Don't waste my time. Give it back!
But this looks like a trap, guys.
Tommy found him, right?
Yes.
A man has been arrested
for allegedly being involved...
...in organ trafficking syndicate
in the international black market.
Dr. Siva, 48, has been
remanded for seven days.
Authorities arrested the
suspect this morning.....
What a fool!
He let himself get caught.
I will take care of this, Dad.
We will find out
who is responsible...
...and we will make them pay.
I will make sure of this.
Weren't you there?
Yes, Siva asked me
to leave earlier.
Siva asked you to leave earlier,
so you left?
Honey.
Tommy will handle it, honey.
There's a Malay proverb
that goes...
..."If you're always angry,
you will get older even faster."
I want my Tan Sri Hamdan...
...at that party later...
...to be as calm as ever.
Not angry like this.
Let's go.
Don't get angry.
Empty.
Is there even a show?
Welcome, Mr. Fariq.
Mr. Ujang. Ms. Wawa.
Without further ado, I'd like
to invite Mr. Fariq to the stage.
Hold on.
Who are you?
Me?
Your number-one fan.
So sweet.
Do you know us?
-Of course, I do.
Who doesn't? Night Spark.
Do you want me to read
your resumes or something?
Resume? We have resumes?
Straight to the point, will you?
-Sure, of course.
No problem.
Just take it...
...as your way of repaying me...
...for the help I've given you...
...at Dr. Siva's house, Mr. Fariq.
Let's get in.
All right. Mr. Ujang.
Ms. Wawa, you can have a seat.
Thank you, Mr. Fariq.
Today.
I will steal...
...your watch.
Just my watch?
I've come so far.
All right, do it.
Misdirection.
Brother.
Misdirection number two.
What do you actually want?
Yes.
Okay, where did he go?
I've been following
you guys for three years.
And I also know...
...why you guys robbed
Dr. Siva's house.
How do you know us?
I made sure not
to leave any traces.
Come on, I'm a magician.
The Heart of Kesuma
once belonged to...
...Princess Adiratna.
-What movie is this?
King Bayu travelled the world...
...in search of
the finest gemstone...
...and the best goldsmith...
...all in pursuit of marrying
Princess Adiratna.
Princess Adiratna and King Bayu
lived happily until fate tore...
...them apart.
-Today, the Heart of Kesuma...
...is worth USD25 million.
Owned by Puan Sri Rubiah Tan.
Wife of Tan Sri Hamdan Tan.
What does Heart of Kesuma
have to do with us?
It does, Mr. Fariq.
I need you three...
...to steal Heart of Kesuma.
I have a plan.
We can do it,
but we don't have any plan.
Question.
Why must we help you?
This man is awesome.
I've been off the radar...
...because I was looking
after my mum.
My mum has cancer.
So I'm in need of a lot of money.
As if.
But you've done so many
big shows all this while.
For the VIPs.
Private shows for the royalties.
Don't tell me you didn't
save up any money?
I was planning on retiring
after the show that night.
I think you know why.
So that's why I need
the money to pay my debt.
Like I said I've been
following you guys for so long.
And I know...
...your target is Tan Sri Hamdan.
Okay.
I know...
...you feel small and inferior.
Compared to him
who's way bigger.
As big as a giant.
That's why you attacked
those around him.
Imagine this.
If we manage to
steal Heart of Kesuma,...
...his wife's favourite necklace.
That means more
than stealing his money.
We get to destroy his ego...
...and it's a knockout
punch to his pride.
Thank you for this information.
We will...
...discuss and
rob it ourselves, right?
You can't do this without me. Why?
Because...
...Hamdan is retiring soon.
He's organising a farewell party
before he moves to Hong Kong.
Ms. Wawa, guess who's going to...
...have a show on that night?
I'm the ticket you've been
looking for all this while.
You can't do this without me.
And I myself...
...could not do it...
...without the help from you three.
I told you...
...that I'd steal your watch.
Hold on.
Wallet.
A thief doesn't tell
anyone anything.
Awesome.
I'll give you one day.
Think about it.
Gosh, he's really into it.
Yeah, all praise be to God.
There'll be a new
caretaker here.
Really? All praise be to God.
See? He's busy taking
pictures of the kids.
He said it was for the profile.
I don't know much.
It's not that easy to understand
these business things.
That's right.
No wonder. Madam.
-Yes.
I have something to give you.
Oh, God. Thank you, Fariq.
-You're welcome.
For never forgetting us.
It's fine, it's not
that big of a deal.
After this, we're
moving to a new house.
It's more comfortable for them.
There'll even be a nurse
who'll take care of these kids.
Gosh, that's nice.
Fariq. Will you still
come and see me?
Of course, no matter
where you go, I'll find you.
Hold on.
I never forgot.
But I can't do magic.
Thank you, Fariq.
-You're welcome.
Ask him.
Ujang's good at it.
She's so happy.
Everyone ready to see magic?
Yes!
What's the magic word?
-Ujang!
The best!
Fariq.
I couldn't find anything
related to Maya.
We've been trying to
bring him down for years...
...but he won't budge.
Hamdan is quite strong.
But...
...he's retiring soon.
He's moving to Hong Kong and...
...I think this is
our chance, guys.
I know, but I'm not
comfortable at all.
We've never worked
with anyone else.
I do understand, Wa.
But I was reminded
of what Hadi said.
Why are we doing all this?
We want to defend
the fate of the oppressed.
Is this the actual place?
I thought he'd have class
and used a warehouse instead.
Is a warehouse that classy?
Night Spark's hideout is at a
warehouse, the rent is expensive.
That's right.
Char Kuey Teow!
Yes?
Hi.
Welcome to my humble abode.
So with the presence
of the three of you,...
...I assume you accepted
the proposal...
...of USD25 million
robbery mission.
We're not here to
listen to your speech.
What's your idea...
...in stealing Heart of Kesuma?
Magic is not just a
trick or a big surprise.
But it's about
the audience's mind...
...and the imagination
they create for themselves.
The connections they
make with what they see...
...and the stories they
create for themselves.
Magic is not just an act.
But it's in the space
between what they see...
...and what we want to believe.
The illusions and tricks
we create together?
Stop playing with us.
If you're really serious,...
...be serious.
You have so many gadgets, Hadi.
Guys, he's here.
He's gone again. He's awesome.
Let's go back. It's
such a waste of time.
Just call us.
You're seeing...
...but you're not
looking at it carefully.
During a real robbery,...
...do you think we
have time for all this?
Ms. Wawa.
I'm not playing.
Take this as a
practice for our robbery.
This is a warning to all of you!
Don't you ever steal
from the Tan Family!
I don't know who's detest us.
Siva is a nice guy.
He has helped so many people.
Will you help him, Tommy?
-Do you think...
...I'm just going
to sit here and do nothing?
Where is my laptop?
Do you see anything suspicious?
No.
Why was Hadi there?
We're going to rob
the most secured,...
...protected jewellery
in front of their own eyes.
All right.
Excuse me.
Ms. Wawa, your order?
-It's fine.
Order, or I won't continue.
Orange juice.
-Orange juice.
Interesting choice.
Ujang?
Cola.
-Cola?
Not afraid of diabetes.
Oh, okay.
Pulled tea.
-Pulled tea?
It suits your age.
What? You asked us to
order but they're all the same.
They're all the same?
Look again. One, two, three.
Please drink.
-You've been gone for so long.
How will you perform at that party?
Puan Sri Rubiah Tan.
She's actually obsessed with me.
I've been gone for four years.
And in that four years,...
...she has asked
her stepson, Tommy...
...to look for me.
Hadi, where have you been?
I haven't seen you in a long time.
I tell you what. I really miss
watching your performances.
Puan Sri, sorry.
We have to get to the vault now.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you follow me?
There's so much that
I wanted to tell you.
Actually, Puan Sri
Rubiah loves attention.
So I agreed to her suggestion.
Tan Sri will put
Heart of Kesuma on her...
...in front of everyone...
...on that night.
So, where's the real
Heart of Kesuma?
I have no idea.
No idea?
Rehearsal time?
-None.
Heart of Kesuma will be
brought in using a security box...
...that looks like an ice box
in the vault under the stage.
Two hours before the celebration
and only the Tan family...
...can have access to the vault.
The vault is under the stage?
-Yes, the vault is under the stage.
And as I said earlier...
...only Tan Sri Hamdan's
family has the access.
Hi, honey.
I'm going into the vault.
Don't forget the password, okay?
-Once the vault door is opened,...
...we only have one minute
to key in the password.
The security ice box
looks like this?
The security box...
...is bulletproof, fireproof...
...and of course can only be
opened by Tan Sri Hamdan only.
And this is...
...my magic box.
Nothing is happening.
Magic.
If we can't open the safe,
how are we going to rob it?
That's my job.
I have to convince Puan Sri...
...to put my magic box
into the vault...
...and I need you guys to
switch Heart of Kesuma.
But there are many guards there.
Cameras are all over.
What should we do?
That's why I need...
...your skills.
Let us survey first.
Recce first.
No problem.
I'll upgrade your gears.
Sorry.
It's my first day.
Hi, boss.
You're the new kid?
Yes, it's my first day.
-Okay.
Wa, done.
-Got it.
I can't see the vault door.
Someone needs to get down there.
There won't be any
show before Tan Sri's.
So, I can give you two weeks to
make preparations for this place.
Look, Mr. Malik. I need to see the
places where I'm keeping my props.
Tommy told me that you can
only get inside during the event.
It will make my job
difficult if that's the case.
A powerful man like you...
...shouldn't just listen to Tommy.
You are better
than this, Mr. Malik.
You're handsome,...
...smart and you have great hair...
...that's been combed neatly.
It suits you.
Come on, Mr. Malik.
Handsome, right?
-Of course.
Thank you, Hadi.
-Wa, you speak so softly.
I don't care.
This is the furthest
we can go, Mr. Hadi.
Because no one's
allowed to get inside.
Just up to here?
If it's up to here,...
...I've entered this place.
-I'm so sorry, Mr. Hadi.
But you can only imagine...
...what's inside.
Mr. Malik, can you not
think about the passcode?
No, because your eyes, Mr. Malik.
They're telling me the
passcode number now.
Mr. Malik, there's
number two, right?
I told you, Mr. Malik.
Don't look into my eyes.
Five?
Do you want me to go on or what?
No, Mr. Malik. There are
two security officers here.
It'll be over if they hear this.
Mr. Malik.
You should let me go inside.
I promise not to tell Tommy...
...that you have
a slightly weak mind.
Two, five,....
Thank you, Hairul, Ismail.
Don't you want to come inside?
Is there an alarm in the vault too?
Of course.
Whoever tries to
break through this door,...
...carbon dioxide will
come out and fill this vault.
No one will be
alive in five minutes.
Five minutes?
Okay, got it.
Okay, Mr. Malik. That's it.
If you had just given me
earlier, wouldn't it be easy?
I'll leave now, Mr. Malik.
Thank you, Ismail, Hairul.
Thank you.
Good job, everyone.
Now, let's move.
Mr. Malik, how long have you
been working with Puan Sri?
Just recently.
-Just recently? How long?
10 years.
-10 years?
If you had a kid, the kid
would be in standard three now.
Are you married?
-Not yet.
I've got the security alarm...
...for this building
including the vault room door.
But the vault
security alarm system...
...couldn't be found because
it's not in the main server.
We need to find the system
or it'll be like Siva's case.
Wait. But how do you
know Mr. Malik's passcode?
Teach me. That's awesome.
So that I'll know Wawa's secret.
Seriously.
I was just using
the info that I have.
Hey, Hadi.
Night Spark.
Hi, Hadi.
Hi, Sean.
Darn you.
I've invested in your whole tour.
But you...
...decided to just vanish.
Do you know how much I lost, jerk?
Who is this Indonesian man?
Guys. Meet Sean.
My share partner, for my last
magic show four years ago.
I know...
...you're going to perform
during Tan Sri's event.
And you are going to
steal Heart of Kesuma.
Right?
Hold on.
How did you know?
Want me to tell Tan Sri about...
...your evil intentions?
But,
I'd like to know...
...how you're planning to
steal Heart of Kesuma.
By doing it in front
of everyone's eyes.
Wow.
Tell me. How?
You want to tell him?
There's no way.
I don't believe you either.
What would I want to tell him?
Because you can, bro.
Wait.
Let us go.
I'll tell you after that.
-Go.
Suddenly, this is happening.
All right.
This is the original
transparent box.
Okay? I'll put it here.
Now we have to figure out...
...how to make a replica...
...that looks exactly the same.
Luckily, Hadi is doing
it right now, right?
Let me borrow this.
Two hours before the show,...
...Heart of Kesuma will arrive.
At that moment, Hadi and Wawa...
...will be in the vault room...
...with the fake Heart of Kesuma
and the fake box. Get it?
Both boxes, fake and real...
...will be placed in the vault.
After everyone is gone,...
...Ujang and I...
...will break into the vault.
Oh, you?
-Because....
...I'm the only one who
can break into the vault.
Why? Because I'm good at it, bro.
After successfully
disarming the safe's alarm.
Usually, just a minute.
We will swap...
...the genuine Heart of Kesuma
into the fake box.
So this fake box...
...will be carried
onto the platform...
...by Tan Sri Hamdan's security
before being lifted onto the stage.
After that, Hadi will do magic.
Make the box melt.
After Wawa disappears,...
Hadi will invite Hamdan and Rubi...
...to go on stage. Later on,
Wawa will appear again...
...when they are on stage later.
While Wawa is gone,...
...we will replace it with
the fake Heart of Kesuma.
So Wawa is wearing a fake one?
Do you think Tan Sri
is that stupid?
He wouldn't suspect anything if
Wawa just disappeared like that?
I'll convince Tan Sri...
...that Wawa is wearing is
the fake Heart of Kesuma.
Then we'll bring
up the right box...
...with the fake Heart of Kesuma...
and I'll convince Tan Sri...
...that is the true
Heart of Kesuma.
Wait, do you think it's that easy?
We are missing three
important things in this robbery.
First, how do we open the ice box?
That's my job.
-Okay.
Second, how do we disable
the alarm system in the vault?
And third, a replica of Heart of
Kesuma. How do we make it?
Many more have not been settled.
This plan is not yet complete.
That's why we need you, Sean.
Me?
I noticed the logo
near the ice box, Sean.
Don't you have a master key?
One more thing.
I need you to be close...
...to Tan Sri Hamdan,
so that I can hack his cellphone...
...to disable the
alarm in the vault.
I'm the only one who can
be close to Tan Sri, but...
...I'm not a hacker.
That's my job.
Just stay close to him.
Let me hack him.
Sean. You're friends...
...with the appraiser who
auctioned off the Heart of Kesuma.
We need him to replicate
the Heart of Kesuma.
Wait.
There are many things you...
...are not sharing about your plan.
Sean, you know, right?
Heart of Kesuma is
currently worth USD50 million.
Sean, if you agree to this plan,...
...your share is 50 percent.
You'll get USD25 million easily.
If it fails?
If it fails,...
...Tan Sri or Tommy will kill us.
You can get ready
to see us die, that's all.
Just a moment.
We're going off the topic.
What are you talking about?
You told us it's 25 million.
To him, it's 50 million.
You're even asking him to
see us die. What's all that?
Fariq, listen. I'm not taking your
share, right? I'm not doing that.
It's still the same.
Don't be greedy.
You can take 25 million.
-What?
What's all this?
Actually,...
...I like dangerous
plans like this.
I can make money.
If I can't make money,...
...I can see you die.
But I'm afraid.
What if Tan Sri knows
about my involvement?
Then I'll be the one to die.
Tan Sri doesn't even need
to know that you're helping me.
to know that you're in my plan.
I know...
...I owe you money for
the show four years ago.
If you work with us,...
...you'll get even more, Sean.
Why not?
Hadi, tell us.
How can we be a team
and work with you...
...when you lied to us?
-What else aren't you telling us?
Guys.
I'm not betraying anyone right now.
I didn't tell you because...
...he's part of my plan.
And we really need him.
No. Your plan is actually
not to tell us either.
Then, you actually want
Sean to catch us, right?
Yes.
-Why?
Bargaining power, Fariq.
Imagine if we have...
...to beg him now.
It's better that he comes to us.
Besides, we need
him to open the box.
Look. It's already hard
for us to trust you...
...let alone Sean Rahman.
You know Sean Rahman, right?
-Not my type.
Guys.
I'm not asking you to trust me...
...or Sean Rahman.
Now we have the same mission.
Heart of Kesuma.
Greed makes one blind, Hadi.
We've seen it many times before.
Guys.
Please, okay?
Right now,
we need to stick to our plan.
Please.
-Hadi.
This is not about
the plan only, you know?
The three of us are
betting our lives on this plan.
But behind us, you're lying.
No, Hadi.
To be honest,...
...you are not an honest man.
Fariq. Wawa.
Ujang! Guys, come on.
What a waste of time.
Okay, so now we're
just going to stop, right?
The problem is his plan
is dangerous. It's not safe.
He needs us more than we need him.
Here's the plan.
Now, let him face this chaos.
Let's relax.
This time, I can't
afford to fail again.
Tan Sri.
Treasure sword does not age.
Great, Tan Sri. Solid!
Thank you.
Honey.
-Thank you.
I've found a handbag that
matches my dress for the night.
What do you think?
You should buy it.
Thank you.
I'll ask Tommy to
get it for me later.
Don't be like this.
He's just a boy.
Don't be so hard on him.
Because he's just a boy...
...I have to be strict.
Tommy.
Yes.
-How's the investigation on Siva?
I've got a lead, but
I need more time.
You're always saying that.
Can you stop being
a disappointment?
I expect some results, okay?
Honey.
There are many people here.
Remember our gifts for
my Hong Kong partner.
We need to maintain good relations.
The ways of the world.
Got it.
Tan Sri, let's go.
Delina dear.
-Yes, auntie.
I want to get a handbag at TRX.
You're really boring.
You've been quiet since earlier.
Sorry.
I'm thinking hard, actually.
I have this job.
But,...
...I don't know if I should
take it or if I should do it.
Because...
...I don't know them.
I worry that they
might lie or betray us.
How does it feel to be betrayed?
It's not fun, Anna. It hurts badly.
Don't get me wrong. I just worry...
...that if I take on this job,...
...something bad will
happen to Wawa or Ujang.
I don't want that to happen.
I worry about them.
Why are you looking
after Wawa and Ujang?
Because...
...we share the same pain.
We're also orphans.
Hamdan only cares
about cutting costs.
Construction with total
disregard for worker safety.
In the end, our
fathers lost their lives.
Our fathers' lives
it's as if they had no value.
So, I've promised...
...to take care of Ujang and Wawa.
We made a promise to stay together.
Together, we will
ensure Hamdan's downfall.
We'd like revenge.
But who are we to take down
Hamdan who's as huge as a dinosaur?
We can do it,
but in the way that we know.
What Ujang said is true.
This is our only
chance to fight him.
At least you guys know your dads.
I don't even know who my dad is.
Anna.
We're here for you.
Don't say that.
Hadi?
Whose building is this?
Tommy.
Wawa, can you hack
into Hadi's phone?
Done.
-That's fast.
Were you on the phone with him?
What is wrong with you?
Wawa, turn on the speaker.
Who were you helping...
...when Siva's house was robbed?
Who did I help?
Remember?
How would I know?
I only went to
Siva's house to perform.
Who broke into Siva's house?
I'm asking you.
Who?
Tommy.
How many guests were there?
Do you think I know them all?
Aren't you...
...good at doing tricks?
You know? He's
good at doing tricks.
Why don't you just disappear?
Tommy.
Sorry.
I think this is all just
a misunderstanding.
But, please.
Don't hit me too hard, okay?
Now you get to breathe...
...because my stepmother
is obsessed with you.
But don't worry.
After the show.
I'll do the magic.
And just like that,
you'll go missing.
You only have one month to live.
Come in.
Hello, guys.
How are you?
Handsome, beautiful and.....
Silent.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you...
...the true value of
Heart of Kesuma.
And about Sean, I'm sorry.
Why aren't you running?
Tommy threatened...
...to kill you after the show.
Why aren't you running?
You don't have to look
at her like that, okay?
What?
Okay, listen.
Actually, there are two reasons.
Two reasons.
-All right.
The first reason...
...is personal.
I don't think I need to tell you.
Okay.
-But...
Reason number two.
You know, right?
That I really need the
money for my grandmother.
Wait a minute.
Wasn't it for your mum?
Don't you know? A mother...
...is also a grandmother.
We have to call her grandmother...
...because she's in the
paternal grandmother group.
In our lineage, it's a little
different when it comes to Malay.
Right?
That's right.
-See?
Okay, you're right.
-Fariq.
I'm begging you.
I need you, Fariq.
I need Wawa and Ujang.
I can't do this alone.
Please guys, come on.
Come on.
Okay.
Ujang.
Because you passed
the loyalty test.
Is the loyalty test like PLKN?
No, it's not the same.
We need Rubiah's fingerprint...
...and key from Tommy.
Before you got here, I
was settling on number one.
Then, this phone needs to be
placed next to Hamdan's phone...
...and I can hack it.
And this one is for
scanning Tommy's key.
We already know the vault model...
...and Ujang will provide
the same model...
...for me to practise and...
...number five will
also be settled by Ujang.
Look, Wa. I'm important, you know?
Whatever.
So that means you
guys agree to do this?
But we don't trust Sean.
Me too.
All right.
So, this is the one
we have to plan...
...for the set-up.
Nice.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
Nice!
It's settled.
Just look, don't touch anything.
Remember.
It's work.
No promises.
Hello, Puan Sri. Thank you
for seeing us today, Puan Sri.
Hi, Hadi.
That's what I wanted to hear.
How are you, Puan Sri?
-All praise be to God.
This is my assistant, Wawa.
-Hi.
This is Malik.
Remember the first time we met?
Yes, Puan Sri, can you please...
Hi, Malik. How are you?
Are you okay?
You didn't look very well just now.
Puan Sri.
Puan Sri, shall we?
-Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
Puan Sri, this is
the stage set up...
...and also the
proposed colour palette
Hi, Tommy.
-Mother.
Puan Sri, can we have
the lights off, please?
Fariq. Tommy's secretary
is coming to the room.
Hi, boss. Yes, I'll be
waiting in your room.
There's an important
document to sign, very urgent
We'll be using a lot of LED lights.
-I'm going upstairs for a bit.
The idea is here when we use
all this neon, to make it pop.....
To make it pop up, Puan Sri.
To make it pop up
Fariq, Tommy is coming at you.
Estimated time of arrival.
Two more minutes.
We're doomed!
What's the matter with the real
estate proposal near Hong Kong?
Hold on. What should
we do? Fariq.
With the right
lighting and feel,...
...we can give an impression
-I need to go to the toilet.
Are you okay?
-Yes.
Sure. Do you know your way?
Yes. Excuse me.
Okay, so.....
I need the proposal by today.
Tommy.
Hi. I'm Wawa, Hadi's assistant.
I know.
Anything I can help you with?
Yes, I'd like to ask you a favour.
A favour?
Why?
Is the Hadi guy not
paying you enough?
Not enough?
-Seriously, Wa?
Am I not enough?
Of course, it's not enough.
I actually...
...wanted to ask for your number...
...for security purposes.
Or, who knows?
What else do you want, Wa?
What else?
Enough, Ujang. Wawa is giving
us time, so shut your mouth.
Sure.
I'll give you my personal number.
If there's something else that you
want to check, I'm okay with that.
Over dinner?
But you're a very busy man, Tommy.
I can always make time
for a pretty thing like you.
All right, boss.
I'll come by later.
Or do you have anything
else to show me?
Pictures of you?
Tommy.
I definitely love pretty things.
And we're definitely
going to have that dinner.
Going so soon?
-Yes, duty calls, darling.
I will be looking
forward to your message.
Guys, I tried.
Fariq, leave now.
Tommy is near now.
Okay, Puan Sri.
I hope you like my presentation.
Any questions, Puan Sri?
No, Hadi, it's great.
Okay, that's good.
-The proposals are all here.
I love it. Your presentation
is very detailed.
Thank you very much.
So if there's nothing else.
I think I should leave now.
-Why don't you have coffee first?
It's fine.
Maybe next time?
Next time.
Thank you very much, Puan Sri.
Sean.
This looks like a baby oil ad.
Aunties love a body like this.
Put this phone next to
Tan Sri Hamdan's phone.
Then I'll do the rest.
I like smart women like you.
Do you know how to use this phone?
I got this from my contact.
There's a defect.
The bank doesn't want it.
But it's suitable for us.
-This is a 4321, right?
Yes.
This is the original
Heart of Kesuma.
It really can't be replicated.
You won't be able to
match it even with laser.
I can give you any
details you want...
...but I want you to know
about Princess Adiratna.
What is that for?
-For memory.
By the way, I love your glasses.
Oh, okay.
Shall we continue?
Do you really think
Hadi likes Wawa?
Hadi is my idol.
Wawa is the love of my life.
Should I accept it or be jealous?
What do you think I should feel?
I think you should shut up, Ujang.
But what do you think?
Ujang, why are you
thinking about that now?
Ujang, when we're
in the vault later,...
...don't talk like this, okay?
-I'm confused, bro.
The chicken rice
here is really the best.
We haven't asked Hadi.
What will he do with the money?
What do you want to do with it?
Be careful. This thing is fragile.
If it falls, it's
guaranteed to break.
Then how am I supposed to
get away if this thing is fragile?
I'm not done adjusting yet.
Be patient.
Don't rush, honey. Come on.
Let's go out for a while.
Fariq, let's stick
to the original plan.
Listen.
I haven't understood...
...why you're so excited
to do this job, okay?
But it's okay. No need to explain.
I don't even want to know.
Listen, he takes
50 percent of our cut.
He doesn't have to do anything.
We do everything.
Negotiate this properly.
I can't change this deal
until the show is over.
What? Right now, imagine.
What if Sean doesn't want
to give us the passcode?
Okay, listen.
This is the last time.
After that, no more. Bye.
Bye.
-Fariq.....
2 HOURS BEFORE THE SHOW
My beloved necklace.
Hi, Hadi. Hi, Wawa.
-Hi.
Hi, Puan Sri.
-Nice to see you.
Nice to see you too. Please.
-I'll open the vault.
Tommy, the key?
Thank you.
Hello. Excuse me? Tommy.
This is magic. Come on, man.
It's okay, Tommy.
Let him be.
All clear.
I can't wait for your
show tonight, Hadi.
Of course, Puan Sri.
I can't wait for
tonight's show either.
Puan Sri.
Guys, just to inform you guys.
Please raise the box
covered with the blue cloth first.
Come, Puan Sri.
-All right.
But Puan Sri, I promise you.
This show is going
to be something...
...that you will
never forget forever.
This is such a suspense.
Yes, that's the purpose.
Okay, SWAT team.
Check all the perimeters...
...and get back here 15
minutes before the show. Go.
Let's go, Puan Sri.
Don't worry, the Heart of Kesuma...
...and all belongings
are safe in there.
Puan Sri, the
security here is no joke.
What's the matter?
Who did this?
-I have no idea.
Okay, get back to work.
Ready?
Let's go.
We're in. Sean.
Tan Sri. Puan Sri.
Of course, I was born ready.
Okay, let's go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Okay.
Let's go.
Ready, Sean. We
only have one minute...
...once Fariq opens the vault.
It's hard to break in.
Impossible
-Sean, please nod if you're ready.
It's hard to break in?
Yes. Only the owner knows
the passcode to open the box.
I don't know either.
-Sean is so rude.
Whose friend is that?
Okay.
Got it?
-I got it.
Awesome.
Okay.
Second round.
Let's go.
-Okay.
Wa, I know you're hearing this.
But Fariq, do we suit each other?
What do you mean?
-Me and Wawa.
But you know, I
really want a child.
Ujang, do you think we're
at the cafe to talk about this?
Can't you see what I'm
doing? Shut your mouth.
Go on.
Got it?
-I got it.
The key.
Open it.
Guys, wait.
Sean is not ready yet.
If you open it now, you will
trigger the countdown alarm.
What's the matter?
I've already opened it.
What's taking you guys
so long to do your job?
Hurry up, what's all this?
Sean, do you want them to die?
Sean.
USD25 million, Sean.
You guys talk too much.
Tan Sri. Puan Sri.
Okay, go.
Done.
Ready.
Congratulations, Tan Sri.
You get to move to
a new place in Hong Kong.
It's nothing special, Sean.
Even if I move, my mouthpiece
is still in KL.
We're in.
Wa, passcode.
Wait.
-No problem, Wa.
My whole life
I've been waiting for you.
Without you, my life cannot go on.
I love you.
Shut up.
4. 3.
Jang, what you doing?
My work is done.
Fariq, why has it restarted?
I don't like this.
We're doomed. This
system requires you...
...to enter your
passcode every minute.
Otherwise, the alarm will turn on.
Why didn't you tell me?
How would I know?
I never even opened the safe.
Damn it. Why don't you
just tell me next year?
Wait. Quick, Wa.
-Wait.
I'll check, wait.
Datuk Mus.
What now?
Sean, you need to
go to Tan Sri now.
Hurry up.
How are you, my friend?
-I'm fine, Tan Sri.
Thank you very much, Sean.
Their work is easy.
They just talk
We're in sweats down here. If
the system fails, we'll be caught.
Then we'll go to jail.
Have you ever been to jail?
Never.
-Me neither. We are young...
...and cute,
we shouldn't go to jail.
How long do we have, Ujang?
We still have time.
I can tell you're not confident.
Ujang, don't test my patience.
-Wa, what's all this?
He told us to relax,
but now he's losing it.
His biceps seems big, but
he's getting smaller. What?
Ujang. I can hear you
chatting with Wawa, Ujang.
At least you have Wawa.
You can talk all you want.
I don't have a girlfriend, Jang.
I'm not even married yet.
Don't you think I want to get
married or have a baby?
Jang, my baby will surely be cute.
I want to get married, Jang.
I'll strangle you, Sean.
Sean, just 30 seconds.
Hurry up.
This goes here.
This one, here.
-We still can do business together.
Unless I make you busy.....
Oh, my God!
Tan Sri.
This watch is beautiful.
This is a limited-edition.
Okay, I'm back online.
Wawa, 15 seconds.
-Just a moment.
I can't breathe anymore, Wa.
Relax, Fariq.
2, 0,...
...5, 8, 3...
...9, 4, 1.
Done.
Sean. It's important for a
man to have many watches...
...but only one wife.
Tan Sri!
Datuk Lee. Shall we?
-Yes.
Sean, stay close to Tan Sri again.
What a nuisance.
This is adding to my work.
Going to retire and...
...spend some time with her.
Excuse me, Tan Sri.
Yes
Please.
Everyone.
I would like to propose a toast.
4.
7.
5.
6.
Since I was little, he
has been guiding me.
He also taught me a lot
about business and life.
Thank you, Tan Sri.
-All right.
Everyone.
Tan Sri Hamdan Tan.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
8. 1.
Dad, someone wants
to see you over there.
Hadi.
Sean, why won't you go to Tan Sri?
So what do you have for me?
Sorry, Hadi.
This is all I can do.
Sorry. Aunty, let's change
your clothes.
Okay, excuse me. Busy night.
Hadi, I need more time.
Quick.
-Shut up.
Don't say anything.
I didn't say anything.
You look nervous. Wa.
Wa, we don't have enough time.
Help us buy some time, Wa.
I'll treat you to a meal, Wa.
At Hokkaido Table at TRX, Wa.
Please, Wa. What about the time?
We still have time.
Just pray for now.
You have religion, right?
Pray hard.
So?
These numbers are not repeated.
It's a numeric
logic of the pattern.
Then, what's the last number?
0, 2 or 9.
Those are the only numbers
that haven't been used yet.
4, 7, 5, 6, 3, 8, 1
Hurry, Jang. Quick.
Jang, which number do you like?
0, 2 or 9?
What is this? Hurry up.
This is not funny.
Sorry, we really don't
have the last number.
You have to choose now.
I don't know and
I don't want to choose.
Gosh.
-Jang, you have to choose.
Quick, Jang. Quick.
Quick, Jang.
Press 2.
-Press 0.
Got it.
-Got it? Got it, yes!
Yes!
Ujang, hold on.
I'll unlock the lift.
All right. Cover it back up.
Task completed.
Let's go.
Done, let's go.
Were you stressed out earlier?
You said you want to get married.
When did I say that?
Or was it you?
You got a concussion?
-What the heck? Who said so?
I was talking about something else.
Ujang. How did you know
that it was nine?
Did you just make a guess?
You are awesome.
I was only thinking logically, Wa.
You chose zero, Hadi chose two.
But I have to press, right?
I consider myself like a banker.
The banker always wins.
That's why I chose number nine.
What are you doing?
Be gentle. These suits
are expensive. Come on.
Fariq? Ujang?
Why aren't they answering?
-I don't know.
Come on.
-Come on, we have to get ready.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen...
...to the Retirement Ceremony
of Tan Sri Hamdan Tan...
...from the corporate world.
Tonight, we will be celebrating...
...five decades of excellence...
...along with Tan Sri's legacy.
I have told Hadi.
This man really can't be trusted.
Is that so?
Do you think Hadi
would have listened to you?
Because I don't trust you
guys at all either.
Do you think I'll give
him Heart of Kesuma?
And that I'll believe that he'll...
...give it to me after
this show is over?
You're greedy, Sean.
Greedy people always lose.
You don't have to teach me.
I know you do not
agree at all about...
...how the profit is divided.
That's why you're the
person I don't trust the most.
Najib.
Master card.
Thank you.
I almost forgot.
Heart of Kesuma.
What is this?
Why is Heart of Kesuma with you?
Wait.
Hadi.....
Hadi doesn't know about this?
Does Hadi know you backstabbed him?
Beardy, who were you
calling greedy earlier?
Me or you?
I didn't expect
you'd betray Hadi.
You're actually just like me.
Two of a kind.
A true businessman.
I like that.
But...
...this time, I won.
I won.
Actually, I have a special
surprise for Hadi tonight.
I invited the appraiser.
And I told Tan Sri...
...it is a must...
...for the appraiser to check the
authenticity of Heart of Kesuma...
...before Hadi leaves the stage.
He's doomed. Consider
Hadi's debt to me settled today.
Where are Fariq and Ujang?
I hope they won't betray us.
Wait. We might not be good...
...but we won't do that.
Don't simply accuse us.
Okay, I'm only asking.
Let's go.
And I would like to invite...
...Tan Sri Hamdan Tan
with his wife,...
...Puan Sri Rubiah Tan.
Not to forget, their son.
Tommy Tan, and also
his fiance, Ms. Delina.
Please welcome.
Without wasting time,...
...we will begin our
first performance.
This is no ordinary performance...
...because this entertainer
has been in hiatus...
...for four years.
And today,
he returns to give...
...the most special
performance for all of us.
Please give a big
round of applause...
...for the famous
magician in Malaysia.
The Great Hadini.
Good evening.
Tan Sri, Puan Sri.
Datuk Seri, Datin Seri.
Datuk-datuk.
Datin-datin.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Tonight we will celebrate...
...something that knows no time...
...which is love.
Love and affection...
...should be celebrated
in many ways.
Apart from magic.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome my assistant.
Wawa!
Come on, let's get started tonight.
Now. I need a volunteer...
-I'll be back.
...for my next magic show.
I'm sure
there's no one worthier...
...than Tan Sri Hamdan himself.
So, Tan Sri, how are you?
Tan Sri. Please applause...
...for Tan Sri Hamdan!
Tan Sri, this is how
the game works.
I will choose the row number...
...and you will choose
the seat number.
And there, we will guess
if it's a male or female.
And the winner will get...
...RM1,000.
I accept.
-Okay. Then,...
...I'll choose row M.
I choose the number 12.
Number 12.
Okay, Tan Sri. Actually,
I need to tell you that...
...as a great magician
in Malaysia,...
...I have psychic powers.
So, I'll choose...
...female.
Male.
-Male? All right.
So, who's sitting in M12?
Please get up.
It's me, Tan Sri.
Gosh. Tan Sri, I lost.
You owe me RM1,000.
-Of course, Tan Sri.
RM1,000, Tan Sri.
Uncle. Sorry for making
you wait so long.
This is the thing you asked for.
Uncle, whatever you
want is already in this.
How long will it take?
A week. I'll make sure it will be
delivered to your house in a week.
The faster, the better.
My granddaughter's
heart can't wait any longer.
Uncle.
I'll take care of it, don't worry.
Take care, I'm leaving.
Tan Sri, I want to
play another game with you...
...but this time with a price
of RM10,000.
Do you have RM10,00?
Of course, I've got
RM10,000, Tan Sri.
Sure.
Where were the afternoon's guards?
-A change in shifts.
Who's sitting at Y27?
Please get up.
It's me, Tan Sri.
Gosh, Tan Sri. I
lost again, Tan Sri.
RM10,000.
Cash, Tan Sri.
Thank you.
-Tan Sri.
What don't we play one
more game, Tan Sri?
But this time with a value...
...RM100,000.
Are you sure?
-Of course, Tan Sri.
Okay.
-All right. Give it up.
Tan Sri.
There are two levels
in this game.
The first level.
Please choose one card...
...that you see in this deck.
One more time.
I'll slow down a little.
Got it, Tan Sri?
Yes.
-All right.
For the second level,...
...you can choose a
number from one to nine.
It doesn't matter which number.
What's important is
that you have to write it...
...on that paper.
Done, Tan Sri?
-Okay.
The card that you chose.
It's easy, Tan Sri.
Any magician can guess...
...but level two
is not easy, Tan Sri.
Even without any clues or hints.
I know it because...
...I am The Great Hadini.
Thank you, Wawa.
Tan Sri,...
...the card that you chose is...
...Ace of Spades.
Is that right, Tan Sri?
And the number that you chose.....
That's my card!
Hadi.
I owe you RM100,000.
Thank you very much, Tan Sri.
Thank you!
He's great, right?
-Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is
now time for tonight's highlight.
The Heart of Kesuma once
belonged to Princess Adiratna.
King Bayu travelled the world...
...in search of the
finest gemstone.
Standby with the first box.
Send it up now.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Here it is the safest
safety box in the world.
Inside it contains
Heart of Kesuma...
...which once belonged to
Princess Adiratna and now,...
...it is owned by
Puan Sri Rubiah Tan.
Now, this necklace is worth...
...USD50 million.
The maker said
this box is bulletproof,...
...waterproof and fireproof.
But has this box ever...
...been tested by a magician?
Since he claimed that this box...
...is the safest box in the world.
Ms. Delina, may I?
Ms. Delina looks
beautiful with this necklace.
Hadi. What are you doing?
This is not our plan, right?
Yes. Puan Sri.
This is the beauty of magic.
It's all about misdirection.
Puan Sri, don't worry.
That is a fake necklace.
Oh, Puan Sri...
...look at my fingers.
There are traces of gold paint.
And of course, there are traces
of gold paint on the necklace too.
Tan Sri and Puan Sri.
The real Heart of Kesuma...
...belongs to Puan Sri
and it always will.
I was just using magic tricks
to joke around with Puan Sri.
Puan Sri and Tan Sri,
please come up here.
Please.
Sean, it's true.
This box is the safest
in the world.
Even a magician
like me can't open it.
Awesome.
Tan Sri, go ahead.
Thank you.
Honey.
And there you have it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is the Heart of Kesuma...
...once belonged to
Princess Adiratna.
This beautiful necklace
is now around the neck...
...of Puan Sri Rubiah Tan.
Ladies and gentlemen, please
give another round of applause...
...for the amazing
performance by...
...The Great Hadini!
Not so fast.
First of all.
Congratulations, Hadi.
It was an
extraordinary performance.
But there was a piece of advice...
...from my good friend,...
...Mr. Sean Rahman there.
So, he persuaded
me to get an appraiser...
...to appraise the necklace...
...before you leave the stage.
Who knows, right?
It could be fake.
Do you really like it?
-After all,...
...it's all about misdirection.
And we don't want to
miss anything, right?
Thank you.
Heart of Kesuma...
...has survived for centuries.
There is a small chip...
...on the original connecting part.
Puan Sri, may I?
-Yes, you may.
Puan Sri.
This Heart of Kesuma
is original and genuine.
Congratulations, Tan Sri, Puan Sri.
Ladies and gentlemen,...
...The Great Hadini!
Darn it.
How dare he mess with me.
Open!
Damn it.
Look for them until you find them.
Hurry up!
I told you, he couldn't be trusted.
-What a bad luck we have.
Luckily, there's a plan B.
Fariq, hurry up.
-Hold on.
I need to have his style.
-Be careful.
This is the last time and bye.
He is spying on you.
Look up a little.
Looking for inspiration
and hover around.
I go and get a drink first.
Damn you.
Sean's men are behind us!
Follow the plan.
-Okay.
All right.
-Let's go!
Wa, hurry up, your turn.
Okay, yes.
Ujang, ready.
-Roger that.
He's got a gun!
Wait.
Nice.
Let's go!
From nothing...
...until today,...
...I have achieved a lot.
All this is not easy to achieve...
...but with patience
and hard work...
...we were able to succeed.
They are still on our tail.
Yes, I saw it. What do
you expect me to do?
What's the plan?
-It's slippery out, and...
...I haven't had dinner yet.
-Can you both stop arguing now?
Guys, follow me.
-Okay.
They're right ahead.
Guys, go left.
-No way we're turning right.
Oh genius.
What now? Ram through?
-They're behind us.
Now what?
-Quiet, okay?
I just want us to be safe, Wa.
You still have time for that.
Guys, follow me.
-Okay, hurry up.
Okay, Wa. After you.
We can't get through.
On foot now.
Okay.
Turn around!
-Go there!
Wawa.
Ujang.
Where are you going?
You guys are naughty.
Are you trying to trick me?
We did the work.
Are we not going to get anything?
What a pity.
Listen.
Tan Sri will know that
what Puan Sri is wearing is...
...the fake Heart of Kesuma.
And he will ask me to
represent him to destroy you guys.
Najib. One stack.
I told you.
I'm a true businessman.
So,...
...I respect other businessmen.
Take the money and bring it back.
Share it with your friends.
Get out of here.
Fariq.
Don't.
Let's go.
-What?
We worked for USD25 million...
...but we got RM100,000 only.
Wawa, Tommy.
It's all in vain.
We worked like crazy.
In the end, we got nothing. Wawa.
Don't stop hoping.
Hadi.
You did all this for me, right?
Yes.
What is this?
-I don't know.
Guys, let me introduce you to her.
This is Maya.
Tan Sri has arrived.
Tan Sri.
Puan Sri, Tommy.
Tan Sri, I.....
I knew it.
Hadi and the gang must have
planned to steal Heart of Kesuma.
But lucky for you, Tan Sri. I was
able to catch them and take.....
That's right.
I know Hadi wanted to
steal Heart of Kesuma...
...but because you...
...ordered him to.
Tommy.
What is this?
Hey. What are you doing?
Handsome.
-Don't mess with my stuff.
Tan Sri.
I can explain everything
about that photo, Tan Sri.
It's not what it seems.
You trust me right, Tan Sri?
What else do you want to explain?
Where is my wife's necklace?
Do you want a new job?
Wait. So, Tommy's
fiancee is Maya?
Hold on. You stole Heart of
Kesuma for personal reasons.
So this is your reason?
We almost died because he
wanted to see his girlfriend.
Ex-girlfriend. Nice
dress by the way.
I apologise to you all.
I have no intention
of using you guys.
But I have no other
way to meet Maya.
I'm lost without Maya by my side.
How long do I have
to work with Tommy?
I have shared all the
information with you.
Is it not enough?
-Maya.
I promise after Heart of Kesuma,
we will leave all this behind.
I will marry you.
-This will never end, Hadi.
For Heart of Kesuma,...
...you want me
to work with Tommy...
...to get all the security
information about the necklace.
All you care about
is that necklace.
You're so obsessed, you
forgot about my feelings.
You made promises...
...but you never kept them.
Tommy.
He gave me strength
that I needed at the time.
I might have hesitated...
...but I deserve happiness.
That's exactly why I chose Tommy...
...so that I can move on
with my life and forget you.
Four years ago.
I made the plan...
...to spoil the show.
I fake my own
death in front of you.
So you'll realise that...
...I've waited long enough.
I have the right to
choose my future.
It's not just about
feeding your ego.
Are you happy with him?
Just at the beginning.
He's not who I thought he was.
But I can't run
away from him, Hadi.
When you put this
Heart of Kesuma on me,...
...I don't know how I knew...
...that this is the real
Heart of Kesuma.
Because I know you
won't put fake things on me.
You gave Heart of
Kesuma to your girlfriend?
Only Maya can bring
Heart of Kesuma out safely.
So you trust your girlfriend...
...whom you haven't
seen for so long?
It seems that these two
were once in a relationship.
How sweet.
So you did all these...
...to get her.
And did you succeed?
Who do you think you are?
This woman is mine.
She's my property.
Kill them!
Good luck, guys.
Tommy.
Hadi.
Hadi! Hadi!
Hadi!
Guys! Let's go!
Let's go!
You won't get...
...what's rightfully mine...
2 WEEKS LATER
What a pity.
We almost got it.
I didn't think we'd lose Hadi.
Right? Me too.
But it's bound to happen,
so what can we do?
It's sad that Hadi isn't here.
Seriously, his body
hasn't been found?
I am not sure. Maybe he
is still alive? Just like Maya.
Delina, I thought she died
because of falling but she's alive.
She's not only alive...
...but she also got away
with that necklace.
She's really cunning, right?
Parcel.
Okay.
I promised, right? From
your number-one fan.
What is this?
Why, Wa?
What? Wa!
What is this?
-What's the matter, Wa?
Wa, what's up?
25 million?
Wait.
What is this?
Hadi is alive.
Hadi's getting married.
Wa, you and I. What
are we waiting for?
Let's have a double wedding.
I didn't expect to find
Hadi in a place like this.
Relax. At least,
the sea breeze is great.
Hadi!
Hello.
-Hadi.
Fariq.
Hadi!
Ma'am.
Hi.
-Hadi, I want to ask.
That day it really seemed like
you were stabbed. What happened?
Hadi. Hadi.
Hey, woman.
Don't forget your place.
That knife was a spring knife.
That's a magic prop.
A white lie.
...who just held his retirement
announcement a few days ago...
...is suspected of involvement
in an organ trafficking.
Hey, it's your country.
That's their family day.
That must be your doing, right?
I have something
I want to check first.
Okay, let's go.
-Let's go.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
Take care. I'm leaving.
What are you doing?
Right now, tell me from A to Z.
What business do you
have with the Tan Family?
Right now, tell me from A to Z.
What business do you
have with the Tan Family?
Record. Okay.
Action.
So, I got Tommy's number.
I sent him a link.
I hacked his phone...
...and got everything.
Then, it's settled.
Wa, do you still have
Tommy's number?
You said you are loyal to me.
What is this, Wa? Come on, Wa.
Why are you doing
this, even by the beach?
Hadi, the important thing is...
...we've succeeded
in damaging Tan Sri's ego.
That's a slap to his face.
-Yes, sir.
Therefore,.....
Wait.
We have to get a drink first.
Thank you.
-My friends. Okay.
For the downfall of
the Tan family, forever.
But wait.
So I've joined Night Spark, right?
What do you think, Ujang?
-What do you think, Wa?
Okay.
Nice, I can start
bullying you, Ujang.
No, only Wawa can bully me.
If you know what I mean.
Hadi, how's your mother?
She's well, thank God.
-So can we visit?
Don't forget Hadis grandma too.
Don't forget grandaunt too.
If you want to join Night Spark,
we have to visit your mum.